Spock War Posters Collection
Spock War Posters Collection
- Vietnam
  - 1969-1970 Denison Lecture Series presents: Dr. Benjamin Spock on Nov. 9..., undated; Vietnam #26; 56cm / 36cm 2 copies copy one: Green, blue and white; copy two: Green, blue and black (Map-case 59)
    Condition: minor damage to both copies
  - People's Party — More committed to the next generation than to the next election., undated; Vietnam #27; 66cm / 51cm Orange and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Doves flying and people reaching towards the sun
  - "I know it's just a phase Dr. Spock, but he doesn't seem to be outgrowing it!", undated; Vietnam #28; 45.5cm / 60cm (three copies) original; copy two: black on white; copy three: white on black (Map-case 59)
    Description: LBJ dancing around shooting a gun and the Statue of Liberty talking with Dr. Spock at his desk.
    Artist: Kaed (?)
  - I AM A MAN, undated; Vietnam #29; 55cm / 36cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: no illustration
    Printer: Allied Printer
    Condition: Some folds
  - Vietnam Moratorium, undated; Vietnam #30; 61 cm / 46cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Dove flying against the sky
    Artist: John Scheider
    Printer: The Ad Hoc Federal Employees Moratorium Comm.
    Condition: Upper left corner is taped
  - You've Come a Long Way Baby, Vote For the Doctor who got you on, Spock for President, 1972; Vietnam #31; 58cm / 45cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: collage of evolution in the shape of an "S"
    Artist: Rogers
  - Federal Employees Vietnam Moratorium Oct. 15, undated; Vietnam #32; 58cm / 45cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Gathering at the capital
    Printer: Ad Hoc Federal Employees Vietnam Moratorium Committee
  - Benefit for the Minnesota — Dr. Benjamin Spock — Dissent and Social Change.., undated; Vietnam #33; 44cm / 28cm Yellow and black (Map-case 59)
  - The Royal Medical Society Presents an Address by... Dr. Benjamin Spock at the George Square Lecture Theatre..., 4 Jun 1970; Vietnam #34; 39cm / 50cm Red, white, blue and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: no illustration — has several signatures
    Artist: Hero Bros.
  - march against death march against washington, 1969; Vietnam #35; 39cm / 60cm Red, white and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: Tank mobilizing
    Artist: Picasso
    Printer: Reprinted for the new mobilization committee by permission of the artist
  - "We are 1,366 active-duty servicemen"... Join us in Washington November 15 to Bring all the GIs Home Now, undated; Vietnam #36; 58cm / 45cm (two copies) Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Details of the march and a list of the 1,366 servicemen
  - "Two children-raised on Spock! Glad you made it to (?)! The mythical Linda (?)", undated; Vietnam #37; 46cm / 65cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Photo of two girls (Sydney & Diane) playing in a field
  - doctor benjamin spock "dissent in our society"... student service center, October 27, 19?; Vietnam #38; 58cm / 44cm Green, blue, and red (Map-case 59)
    Description: no illustration, has several signatures
  - Against the Wall — Protest Posters of three centuries ..., undated; Vietnam #39; 73cm / 52cm Multi (Map-case 59)
    Description: Painting by Robert Koehler, 1886, "The Strike"
    Artist: designed by Phil Wolfe
    Printer: National Union of Hospital and Health, Care Employees / RWDSU / AFL-CIO
  - For The Naked Truth — Peace & Freedom Party, undated; Vietnam #40; 84cm / 55cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Photograph of businessman and three naked people who are holding hands
    Artist: Shidrousky
    Printer: Emes Printing
  - No rock so hard but that a little wave / May beat admission in a thousand years. Tennyson, undated; Vietnam #40 (reverse); 84cm / 55cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Photo of ocean with waves and a small island
    Artist: Matthew Goyen
  - SAFE RETURN — Artists' Auction For Amnesty, Soho, New York City, January 18, 1975, Vietnam #41; 10cm / 18.5cm Red, white, black and yellow (Map-case 59)
    Description: Colored shapes
    Artist: Calder
  - Peace, undated; Vietnam #42; 89cm / 59cm Gray, blue, purple, white and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: Dove flying
    Artist: BH Moss
  - Q. And babies? A. And babies., undated; Vietnam #43; 97cm / 64cm Multi (Map-case 59)
    Description: Color photograph of a pile of dead men, women, and children
    Artist: R.L. Haeberle
    Printer: Art Workers Coalition
    Condition: Minor damage around the edges
  - "Dear Ben, we are all you children, Pete (?)", 1970; Vietnam #44; 94cm / 61cm White, black and blue (Map-case 59)
    Description: World with a sailboat and oil spill
    Artist: William Hofmann
    Printer: The Hudson Sloop Restoration Inc.
    Condition: Major damage on the bottom half, several folds
  - Cleaver For President — Peace and Freedom Party, Black Panther Party, undated; Vietnam #45; 97cm / 64cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Woodblock Print of Cleaver
  - Who has a better right to oppose the war?... Student Mobilization Committee to end the war in Vietnam..., 1969; Vietnam #46; 96cm / 61cm Red, white and blue (Map-case 59)
    Description: Young man in a red uniform holding a white dove
    Artist: Richard Avedon / Marvin Israel
    Printer: Darien House, Inc.
  - (no caption), 1969; Vietnam #47; 99cm / 61cm Bright florescent colors (Map-case 59)
    Description: American flag bleeding into other flags
    Artist: Michael Lane
  - SPOCK, 1968; Vietnam #48; 107cm/ 71cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: photo of Dr. Spock
    Artist: DJ
    Printer: Personality Posters Mfg. Co., Inc.
  - hear Dr. Benjamin Spock speak on "CAN AMERICA BE SAVED?" Morning church service September 22 at 10:50 AM, undated; Vietnam #49; 112cm/ 71cm Multi on bright blue background (Map-case 59)
    Description: 3D dove sitting on the top edge
    Condition: damaged edges